Adrian Fernandez

Oxnard, CA • a.fernandez1@live.com • 805-889-8377

Github.com/GammaOmegaDelta • linkedin.com/in/adrianfernandez01/

Software Engineer

Versatile programmer with a background in retail and the study of philosophy. Strengths in adaptability, perseverance, and the ability to think in a more creative way to solve the most complex predicament. Focus on communication, internal and external client experience to create a supportive and productive environment.

Skills

Technical: Ruby, Rails, JavaScript, Vue.js, HTML, C#, CSS, GitHub, Git, Pair-Programming, PostgreSQL

Experience

Actualize | Web Developer

January 2019 – Present

- "Seas the Day": Personally developed an app for the everyday traveler that allows them to view a variety of activities based on their destination and save those activities to their own itinerary list. Utilized Google Maps API to organize the activities by distance to show the user the most efficient way to enjoy their itinerary.
- **Bootcamp:** Completed an intensive, 4-month Actualize boot camp & learned various programming languages including Ruby, Rails, HTML, JavaScript. Gained insight on how to handle new technology and learned to foresee challenges a software engineer may encounter.

Carnegie General Insurance Agency | Underwriter

March 2017 – August 2017

- Supported Brokers with premium verifications, communicated changes to their client's vehicles & provided live updates of any ongoing cases.
- Conducted thorough verifications to ensure client data meets company protocol.
- Audited client information to ensure accuracy and report any discrepancies for corrections to Underwriting leads.

Restoration Hardware | Sales Associate

June 2016 – November 2016

- Developed an ongoing trusted relation with clients which increased loyalty for optimized lifetime sales revenue.
- Provided honest and confident feedback to customers regarding merchandise conformity

Van Heusen | Floor Supervisor

May 2015 – May 2016

- Led and coached a team of 3 people to surpass daily sales goals & maximize revenue.
- Trained 8 new employees on company values, standards, and expectations.
- Merchandised products by studying advertising, sales promotions and floor plans.
- Analyzed financial hourly & closing reports for profitability ratios & adjusted daily sales goals accordingly.

Other: Sales Associate | November 2012 – May 2015

Education

Actualize Coding Bootcamp | Certificate of Completion in Computer Science

2019 - 2019

Ventura College | Coursework towards a Bachelor of Arts in Philosophy

2012 - 2015